<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BushTripInjector xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" Id="BushTripInjector">
  <MinVersion>
    <Major>2</Major>
    <Minor>4</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>4276</Revision>
  </MinVersion>
  <PrevVersion>
    <Major>3</Major>
    <Minor>0</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>-1</Revision>
  </PrevVersion>
  <CurrentVersion>
    <Major>3</Major>
    <Minor>0</Minor>
    <Build>1</Build>
    <Revision>4460</Revision>
  </CurrentVersion>
  <ChangeLog>&lt;meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html;charset=UTF-8'&gt;&#xD;
3.0.1.4460 &#xD;
UPDATE: *SPB-Viewer/Compiler:* Updated the property definitions to Sim Update 13 (1.34.16.0)&#xD;
UPDATE: *Databases:* Updated the main, parking and navigational database to Sim Update 13 (1.34.16.0))&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Preflight-Check:* Fixed an issue that prevented opening a BTI file with a title longer than 50 characters. This should not be so strict and only apply to the title of the marketplace product. All apologies!&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
3.0.0.4450 - 3rd Anniversary of BushTripInjector&#xD;
 *This Version has many changes in the core functionality of BushTripInjector. Despite intensive testing, bugs and problems may occur.&lt;br&gt;If you have an issue, please contact me on Discord: &lt;a href="http://discord.bushtripinjector.de"&gt;BushTripInjector Discord&lt;/a&gt;. Thank you very much.*&#xD;
&#xD;
 * 'GUI Improvements'* &#xD;
 *MSF Intro-Screen:*&#xD;
Shows the selected date and time and the corresponding lightness on the introduction screen if individual date and time information is used for the leg.&#xD;
Shows the aircraft at the individual position on the introduction screen if the aircraft has a specific position for that leg.&#xD;
&#xD;
 *Event&amp;Triggers*&#xD;
The *ShowOnMap* Button in Flightplan, Event&amp;Triggers-Editor and Database will not remove other objects from WorldMap when the Ctrl-Key is pressed.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
 * 'Features and Functions'* &#xD;
 *Compiler:* &#xD;
BGL: Added the possibility to compile BGL of different types into the project. Add our BGL source folders into PackageSources\BGL.&#xD;
VisualEffects: Added the possibility to compile VisualEffectLibraries into the project. Add our VisualEffectLib source folders into PackageSources\VisualEffectLibs.&#xD;
&#xD;
 *Event&amp;Triggers*&#xD;
Added a "ExcludeLivingExclusion" to remove static aircraft, airport vehicles, freeway traffic and scheduled and random boats and ships.&#xD;
Added "PlayMusic, ForceMusic and StopMusic" actions to Event&amp;Triggers Editor on request of a commercial customer. &#xD;
The possibility to create a ProximityTrigger, ActivationObjects and Areas to LibraryObjects by clicking a button has been added.&#xD;
&#xD;
 *DiscoveryFlights:*&#xD;
Implemented a solution for Microsoft World-Updates to play WWISE MusicTracks, MusicSegments and MusicPlaylistContainers from Wwise-MusicBank and Wwise-Package files.&#xD;
&#xD;
 *Marketplace:* &#xD;
Added the possibility to add up to 4 more background images / base images.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
 * 'Improvements and Fixes'* &#xD;
 *Aircrafts:* Added Aero Ae45 + Ae145 to the payware aircraft list&#xD;
 *Preflight-Check:* The latest SDK does not accept titles with more than 50 characters. The preflight check now verifies this.&#xD;
 *Databases:* Updated the main, parking and navigation database to AIRAC 2309 (MSFS UPD Sept21)&#xD;
 *Parking-Database:* Added the radius of the parking spot into the parking database.&#xD;
 *Reposition per Leg:* When using parking spots for starting partial legs, other aircrafts are excluded from the use of these spots.&#xD;
 *Landing Challenges:* Landing Challenges are now available for all users in non-experimental environments!&#xD;
 *Release-Notes:* Fixed an issue with the window preventing all information from being visible under certain circumstances.&#xD;
 *Wiki:* Fixed an issue reading specific items from Spanish Wikipedia server.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
</ChangeLog>
  <Downloadlink>https://www.bushtripinjector.de/downloads/</Downloadlink>
  <RequiredDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>14</Minor>
    <Build>5</Build>
    <Revision>1</Revision>
  </RequiredDbVersion>
  <CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>34</Minor>
    <Build>16</Build>
    <Revision>0</Revision>
  </CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
  <CurrentMainDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>34</Minor>
    <Build>16</Build>
    <Revision>0</Revision>
  </CurrentMainDbVersion>
  <CurrentParkingDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>34</Minor>
    <Build>16</Build>
    <Revision>0</Revision>
  </CurrentParkingDbVersion>
  <CurrentNavAidsDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>34</Minor>
    <Build>16</Build>
    <Revision>0</Revision>
  </CurrentNavAidsDbVersion>
</BushTripInjector>