<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BushTripInjector xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" Id="BushTripInjector">
  <MinVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>10</Minor>
    <Build>3</Build>
    <Revision>1742</Revision>
  </MinVersion>
  <PrevVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>1</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>-1</Revision>
  </PrevVersion>
  <CurrentVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>1</Minor>
    <Build>4</Build>
    <Revision>2519</Revision>
  </CurrentVersion>
  <ChangeLog>&lt;meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html;charset=UTF-8'&gt;&#xD;
1.1.4.2519&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: World Update 8 - Iberia&#xD;
UPDATE: *Language:* Added pt-PT as supported language in BTI. Bem-vindo a Portugal.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* New databases are delay for 2-3 days. My BGL-Reader is broken after WU8, I need to fix it first. &#xD;
UPDATE: *Modify Airport:* Added the option to cancel and revert the changes.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Create Airport:* Added the option to override existing airports.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Flightsim.to:* Adjustments to new flightsim.to add-on download format.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.3.2500&#xD;
USER-REQ: *KML-Export:* Export your Flightplan as KML to open it in Google Earth or any other tool of your choice.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Extra-Menu:* The "Clear Message Cache" item has been renamed to "Reset All Messages" for clarity.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Spb-Viewer:* Updated the Property-Definitions to Sim 1.23.12.0&#xD;
BUGFIX: *ModelLibBrowser:* Fixed an issue that prevented the ModelLibBrowser from opening (thanks FronTech).&#xD;
BUGFIX: *ModelLibBrowser:* Fixed an issue that prevented ModelLibBrowser from displaying the already loaded models.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Startup Handling:* Added sync of threads at startup to avoid clicks on the GUI before the GUI is ready to process clicks.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Images:* Fixed an issue when creating content info thumbnails with incorrect image sizes.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Airport-File:* The custom airport is no longer saved in a separate file when using the BTI file format.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.2.2476&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Dependencies:* Define Dependencies to other packages. This feature is only available when using BTI Fileformat. You will find the Name and Version in the manifest of the used package. Versions are detected automatically. Dependencies of those dependencies will be added automatically in most cases.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* Updated internal database for airports and runway to Sim Version 1.23.12.0 Sim Update 8. Several changes in elevation and magnetic declination. Some runways have therefore been renamed.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* Updated the parking database package again.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Steam:* Better message when BTI couldn't compile the mission with link to manual.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *TTS:* Fixed a CTD in TTS Window.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.1.2460&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Dark mode:* An issue in dark mode with CTD at startup has been fixed.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Translate:* Fixed an issue with the translation window when trip fails to compile&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Change language:* Fixed an issue when changing the project language if trip cannot be compiled&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Flight Log:* An issue with creating the flight log has been fixed when trip cannot be compiled&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.1.2442&#xD;
PRO-VERSION: *MediaSlider/MediaScroller:*&lt;br&gt;Added the option to add images for marketplace MediaSlider and Media Scroller. This feature is only available when using BTI Fileformat.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Flight book:* Added the option to include the DialogAction and InstructorDialogAction texts for ProximityTriggers bound to areas on waypoints. Thanks to FronTech.&#xD;
UPDATE: *WebView2:* Updated the WebView2 components to most recent version.&lt;br&gt; *Please delete the "runtimes" folder in your BushTripInjector-Installation.*&#xD;
UPDATE: *Refuel:* Check for Gas-Stations in Parking-Database and not only for the fuel-flags in airport definition. MSFS doesn't have correct fuel-flags for many small airports.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Translation-Window:* Added a notification about not applied data when closing the window via cancel or the X in the title bar.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Translation:* Better handling of non-supported languages of DeepL-API.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Translation:* Performance optimizations. &#xD;
BUGFIX: *SaveAs:* However, the *Save As* menu was not visible for everyone (Thanks Koschi).&#xD;
BUGFIX: *3D Image Generator:* Fixed an issue prevents starting 3D Image Generator when using a flightplan without airports. (Thanks bhpowell)&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Load Mission:* Fixed an issue loading the mission when a BTI converted airport with a starting runway with a true heading between 0 and 10 was selected. (Thanks bhpowell)&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Basedata:* The slipped "Change - Project - Language" button has been moved to the right place again&#xD;
BUGFIX: *LicenseRequest:* Fixed an issue where the text file could not be created.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Anti-Meridian-Crossings:* Fixed an issue with refueling airports when your trip crosses the anti-meridian.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.0.2376&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* Updated internal airport and runway database to sim version 1.22.2.0. 622 added airports, 56 deleted airports. 1414 new runways, 196 runways removed. Details see db_changelog.txt included in this package.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* Also the park database has been updated to sim version 1.22.2.0. Please note that this is a separate file for download. &#xD;
UPDATE: *AirportCreation:* Calculation of magnetic declination when creating airports. For already created airports, magnetic declination is only calculated if it is not currently set.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Parking-Db:* Fixed an issue when checking for parking database updates.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *AirportCreation:* Fixed an issue with the creation of airports: Runways did not reach the internal database correctly. This resulted in invalid airports in your mission. We apologize for this. Thanks to Brad Allen for pointing this out.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *CTD:* Fixed an issue where BTI can crash to desktop if no runway surface can be detected.&#xD;
</ChangeLog>
  <Downloadlink>https://flightsim.to/file/4131/bushtripinjector</Downloadlink>
  <RequiredDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>14</Minor>
    <Build>5</Build>
    <Revision>1</Revision>
  </RequiredDbVersion>
  <CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>23</Minor>
    <Build>12</Build>
    <Revision>0</Revision>
  </CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
</BushTripInjector>