<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BushTripInjector xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" Id="BushTripInjector">
  <MinVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>6</Minor>
    <Build>6</Build>
    <Revision>889</Revision>
  </MinVersion>
  <PrevVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>7</Minor>
    <Build>7</Build>
    <Revision>1046</Revision>
  </PrevVersion>
  <CurrentVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>8</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>1092</Revision>
  </CurrentVersion>
  <ChangeLog>&#xD;
0.8.0.1092&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: Unlocking the Secret of 'AssistancePresets'!&#xD;
 *Your Controls:* BushTripInjector gives you the control over all assistance options. It is your choice which settings are set and whether they should be unlocked for the user.&#xD;
Attention: Not all combination could be testet, some of the settings may not work or break the BushTrip. Please check your desired settings with your trip.&#xD;
&#xD;
USER-REQ: Paste Coords from Google Maps (and others) into Landmarks-Dialog (koschi)&#xD;
USER-REQ: Determinate the Altitude of Landmark in Landmarkwindow.&#xD;
UPDATE: New Runway Surfaces for Airport Creation: FOREST, GRASS_BUMPY, HARD_TURF, LONG_GRASS, SHORT_GRASS, URBAN and WRIGHT_FLYER_TRACK&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed another thing for crazy steam installations (seems to be steam fix weeks again)&#xD;
UPDATE: *Some better Map REST-API Handling to investigate an issue with expired SessionIds.*&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
0.7.9.1078&#xD;
A small intermediate update in front of a bigger thing.&#xD;
&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed a bug for steam and DVD version, if the link is configured to run as admin. (BigLightbolt)&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed a bug on startup, if community folder is not accessible (f99mlu)&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed a bug for refueling after leaving the trip (koschi)&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
0.7.8.1056&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: BushTripInjector introduces 'Landmarks'!&#xD;
Define your own highlights of your tour with your own POIs: Cities, Fauna, Landmarks&#xD;
Just right click in the WorldMap to add a new POI.&#xD;
&#xD;
UPDATE: Startup Optimization: Parallel loading of Airport, Runway and Parking Database.&#xD;
If you encounter some issues, set 'LoadDatabaseParallel' to 'False' in BushTripInjector.ini &#xD;
UPDATE: If BTI detects steam, but no params to compile are set, detect them from steam&#xD;
UPDATE: Performance optimizations Logger.&#xD;
</ChangeLog>
  <Downloadlink>https://flightsim.to/file/4131/bushtripinjector</Downloadlink>
  <RequiredDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>14</Minor>
    <Build>5</Build>
    <Revision>1</Revision>
  </RequiredDbVersion>
  <CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>15</Minor>
    <Build>8</Build>
    <Revision>0</Revision>
  </CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
</BushTripInjector>