<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BushTripInjector xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" Id="BushTripInjector">
  <MinVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>9</Minor>
    <Build>2</Build>
    <Revision>1288</Revision>
  </MinVersion>
  <PrevVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>9</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>-1</Revision>
  </PrevVersion>
  <CurrentVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>9</Minor>
    <Build>2</Build>
    <Revision>1371</Revision>
  </CurrentVersion>
  <ChangeLog>&lt;meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html;charset=UTF-8'&gt;&#xD;
0.9.2.1371&#xD;
UPDATE: *Productkey &amp; Activation*&lt;br&gt;With this version you need a Productkey to run BushTripInjector. Fill out the in-app registration form and send it by mail as requested.&lt;br&gt;Please allow up to 24h for grant.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Swap Action in ProximityTrigger:*&lt;br&gt;In Events&amp;Triggers Editor, now you can swap the actions between Enter (Fly-In) and Exit (Fly-Out) actions.&#xD;
USER-REQ: Show changelog on first start of an updated BushTripInjector.&#xD;
UPDATE: Some changes and additions in the EULA/Terms and Conditions&#xD;
UPDATE: Replaced the outdated maps key with a new one.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Anti-Meridian-Handling* &lt;br&gt;Fixed an issue when the trip goes over antemeridian, and the second part is deeper over antemeridian than the first one.&lt;br&gt;Known issue: Scenery and Landmark pushpins are not shown.&#xD;
UPDATE: *SPB-Viewer*&lt;br&gt;Updated the Property Definitions for SPB-Viewer to Sim-Version 1.17.3.0&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed an issue with adding Landmarks from Flightsim.to or LittleNavMap Userpoints when no further Landmarks are present.&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed an issue with removing HTML-Tags for TTS when "no translation" is selected.&#xD;
UPDATE: some changes to EULA&#xD;
UPDATE: Moved some local computing parts of BTI into the cloud.&#xD;
UPDATE: Removed some typos (and add some more :) )&#xD;
UPDATE: Updated dependencies/NuGet packages (Microsoft.Xaml.Behaviors)&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
0.9.1.1288&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Show invalid triggers in another font color.*&lt;br&gt;Some uses do not see the *"INVALID"* statement in Events&amp;Triggers Editor, so the invalid triggers are now written in red.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Load Aircrafts and Liveries from Official Folder*&lt;br&gt;Load all *free* aircrafts and liveries from Official folder. Those can be selected as aircraft in base data-sheet.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Colored markers for Departure and Destination:*&lt;br&gt;The markers in WorldMap and the Overview Image for the sim are now colored in green (departure) and red (destination).&#xD;
FEATURE: *Added 3 more languages for localization!*&lt;br&gt;Let's welcome * 'suomi'*, * 'norsk bokmål'* and * 'svenska'*!&#xD;
FEATURE: *Use Flightsim.to Scenery-Objects as Landmarks*&lt;br&gt;Import the flightsim.to scenery data into the landmarks. You can select them for the landmark creation to show the POI markers on your bush trip.&#xD;
FEATURE: *Use LittleNavMap UserPoints as Landmarks*&lt;br&gt;Copy your LittleNavMap Userpoints-file into the folder "UserPoints" of your BushTripInjector. With this version, you can add them as landmarks at Landmark-Sheet.&lt;br&gt;Compatible with LittleNavMap Userpoint files (csv) for Import and Export, ie. VRP files or BushTalkRadio POIs.&#xD;
FEATURE: Select/Deselect Flightsim.to Add-Ons from Worldmap&lt;br&gt;With the context menu it is now possible to select and deselect Flightsim.to sceneries.&#xD;
FEATURE:Implemented the possibility to delete multiple landmarks at once&#xD;
UPDATE: Adjust Altitude of Landmarks in background&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
0.9.0.1272&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: BushTripInjector integrates Scenery-Map from Flightsim.to&#xD;
 *Show Add-Ons of Flightsim.to on map and grid.* Select your preferred add-ons and generate a template for your project page!&#xD;
Find great add-ons for Airfields and Airports, Airstrips and Smaller Airfields, Bridges, Buildings, Castles, Cities/Towns/Villages, General Scenery, Helipads, Mountains and Nature, Regional Packages and Stadiums to integrate in your Bushtrips.&#xD;
More than 5700 add-ons available, daily growing.&lt;br&gt;Direkt link for each add-on to the project page on Flightsim.to&#xD;
 *Select on WorldMap-Page:* &lt;br&gt; *All* - show all add-ons (slow)&lt;br&gt; *Trip* - Show add-ons of the trip bounding box&lt;br&gt; *Leg* - Build bounding boxes for each leg and show inside add-ons&lt;br&gt; *Waypoints* - same as legs, only for Waypoints&#xD;
 *Many thanks to Flightsim.to for cooperation.*&#xD;
&#xD;
FEATURE: *Activated the AirportLandingTrigger in Events&amp;Trigger Editor!* &lt;br&gt;Already used to enable fueling on airports, it is now unlocked for use in E&amp;T. Refueling will be merged when generating a trip.&#xD;
FEATURE: *Added the OneShotSoundAction to Events&amp;Triggers Editor.* &lt;br&gt;Plays soundfiles one time for events. Because of the well known sim bug, they will not be played after you left a trip and re-join it.&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed an issue in Event&amp;Triggers Editor that activate the triggers after load, altough user deactivated them&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed an issue with ProximityTrigger didn't detect invalid actions in some cases.&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed a bug detecting changes on landmarks&#xD;
UPDATE: Remove some HTML Tags in TTS, when no localisation is used.&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed an issue that prevent triggers to be included in the Xml/Spb file when they are using CountAction, ObjectActivationAction, ResetTimerAction and/or TimerAdjustAction (Koschi)&#xD;
&#xD;
</ChangeLog>
  <Downloadlink>https://flightsim.to/file/4131/bushtripinjector</Downloadlink>
  <RequiredDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>14</Minor>
    <Build>5</Build>
    <Revision>1</Revision>
  </RequiredDbVersion>
  <CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>17</Minor>
    <Build>3</Build>
    <Revision>0</Revision>
  </CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
</BushTripInjector>
