<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BushTripInjector xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" Id="BushTripInjector">
  <MinVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>2</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>2667</Revision>
  </MinVersion>
  <PrevVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>2</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>-1</Revision>
  </PrevVersion>
  <CurrentVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>3</Minor>
    <Build>3</Build>
    <Revision>2999</Revision>
  </CurrentVersion>
  <ChangeLog>&lt;meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html;charset=UTF-8'&gt;&#xD;
1.3.3.2999 - FPS BOOST&#xD;
BushTripInjector analyzes and optimizes your triggers. This will increase the performance within the simulator by 100% or more for large missions with more than 100 triggers. For now only available for TTS selected and created in the flight plan. The implementation for TTS from the WorldMap and the E&amp;T trigger is already planned.&lt;br&gt;To enable this feature, experimental features must be enabled in the options. BTI automatically analyzes and optimizes the mission during generation. Since these are experimental features, bugs and errors may occur. *Please report working and not working missions.* &#xD;
&#xD;
FEATURE: *Debug-Mode:* When Debug Mode is enabled in Options sheet, BushTripInjector adds several TTS to FlowState, Timeline and automatically generated triggers.&#xD;
FEATURE: *Drag'n'Drop:* Drop SPB files or ZIP files containing SPB files into BTI Mainwindow to decompile the SPB and display the xml file.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *&lt;a href="https://www.bushtripinjector.de/"&gt;BushTripInjector.de&lt;/a&gt;:* Consider the system settings regarding DarkMode/LightMode of the user.&#xD;
UPDATE: *SPB-Viewer:* More modern representation of decompiled spb.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Internal:* Several optimizations and preparations for upcoming features.&#xD;
UPDATE: *SU9-BUG:* Implemented a workaround for a bug in SU9 that prevented the FlowState/TimeLine of a bush trip from being activated. This could lead to the end of the mission not being recognized correctly. To activate the Workaorund, the mission must be regenerated, regardless of whether it was created before or after SU9.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.3.2.2964 - Translation Improvements&#xD;
FEATURE: *Automatic Translation:* A feature has been added in the options to control how the automatic translation via the DeepL API should handle tags within the original language&#xD;
FEATURE: *Automatic Translation:* A feature has been added to control how the distinction and separation of sentences within the original language should be handled via translation with the DeepL API.&#xD;
FEATURE: *Automatic Translation:* A feature has been added to control how translation with the DeepL API should handle the original formatting of sentences.&#xD;
FEATURE: *Automatic Translation:* A feature has been added to control whether the translation with the DeepL API should be more or less formal than the default translation. This is available for the target languages *de-DE* (German), *fr-FR* (French), *it-IT* (Italian), *es-ES* (Spanish), *nl-NL* (Dutch), *pl-PL* (Polish), *pt-PT* and *pr-BR* (Portuguese).&#xD;
FEATURE: *Automatic Translation:* A feature has been added to control how sentences can be manually combined, separated and ignored for translation with the DeepL API in the xml handling. These tags are removed for the simulator when generating and are not part of the mission.&#xD;
FEATURE: *AdvancedMode:* The *AdvancedMode* was introduced to enable some features for experienced users. Currently, *Compile* is additionally available. You can enable this in Options.&#xD;
FEATURE: *Experimental:* In the options you can enable some experimental features in BTI, if available. No experimental features are implemented in this version.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Online-Manual:* Updated the Online manual for the new DeepL-Settings: &lt;a href="https://www.bushtripinjector.de/manual/sim-settings#deepl"&gt;BushTripInjector Manual Options - DeepL&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
UPDATE: *Options:* A few general options have been added to the GUI that were previously only available in the configuration files. For details have a look into &lt;a href="https://www.bushtripinjector.de/manual/sim-settings"&gt;BushTripInjector Manual Options - General&lt;/a&gt;. &#xD;
UPDATE: *ConfigFile:* Save the last selected path to export a model in the configuration file instead of the ini file.&#xD;
UPDATE: *TTS* Added 3 columns to Text-to-speech table: LegNo, WP-Ident and WP-Name. Those are only available for TTS generated by the flightplan and only, if BTI can re-assign them after loading.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Adjust Elevation:* An issue was fixed on startup not to calculate elevations twice.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Adjust Elevation:* Set the mission file to changed only if there was a change in elevations.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Loading TTS:* Fixed an error when loading TTS to the flight plan that prevented the TTS from being correctly assigned to the waypoint. As a result, TTSs to waypoints could be created twice by the user. BTI now displays a message when loading if duplicate TTSs are found for waypoints. &#xD;
BUGFIX: *New missions:* Fixed an issue where when creating new missions, the active flightsim.to add-ons of the current mission were not cleaned up and thus used in the new mission.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *New missions:* Fixed an issue that when creating new missions, notifications were not given to the GUI when changing values in E&amp;T.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.3.1.2926 - Drag and Drop&#xD;
USER-REQ: *SimVars:* Added COM ACTIVE FREQUENCY to the Simulation vars which can be used in Event&amp;Triggers Editor and SinVarWatcher Window.&#xD;
FEATURE: *Drag'n'Drop:* Added the feature to drag and drop BTI mission files. Just drop a BTI file to load the mission into BushTripInjector. &#xD;
FEATURE: *Drag'n'Drop:* Added the feature to drag and drop database files. Just drop the main or parking database file of BTI to install it for use in BTI. It will be copied to your database folder selected on Options Sheet. you can use the ZIP-file or the extracted database.&#xD;
FEATURE: *Append FLT:* Added the feature to manipulate all FLT settings. Enter the settings you want an FLT-Sheet. This feature is only available when you are using BTI file format.&#xD;
FEATURE: *SimVars:* Moved the definitions for Simulation Variables into the Cloud. If you are missing a variable, let me know and I will add it to your BushTripInjector installation.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Event&amp;Triggers/TTS:* Added a warning message when the trip contains 10 or more areas with AltitudeIsAGL which leads to a massive FPS drop in your mission.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Compiler:* Added information message to check spaces in files and directories due to an error in MSFS/FSPackager when compilation fails.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.3.0.2902 - File system restructure (Part II)&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *ConfigFile:* Introduction of the new central config file&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;General Configuration File of BushTripInjector is created at &lt;i&gt;%LOCALAPPDATA%\BushTripInjector\BushTripInjector.config&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Override with command line parameter --configfile "&amp;lt;path and name of your file&amp;gt;"&lt;/li&gt;  &#xD;
&lt;li&gt;General override with environment variable BushTripInjectorConfig=&amp;lt;path and name of your file&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;Command line is prioritized, so you can use them in combination. Environment variables are prioritized in order "Process", "User", "Machine"&lt;/li&gt;  &#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Command line parameter and environment var can use predefined vars: Learn more: &lt;a href="https://www.bushtripinjector.de/manual/commandline-environment/"&gt;BushTripInjector Manual Commandline &amp; Environment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Most parameters of BushTripInjector are converted automatically&lt;/li&gt;  &#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Folders:* New default location for several BushTripInjector files and folders for *new installations*. Existing installations will use after the update the same folders as before. You can change then in *Options*.&lt;br&gt;Learn more: &lt;a href="https://www.bushtripinjector.de/manual/sim-settings/"&gt;BushTripInjector Manual Options&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.bushtripinjector.de/manual/filesystem/"&gt;BushTripInjector Manual Filesystem&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
UPDATE: *File format:* When a LittleNavMap file is opened that has not yet been opened in BushTripInjector, this is automatically saved as a BTI file and no longer in the different SAVES files.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Options:* Added the feature to select the path or set to default for your project files (&lt;i&gt;%PROJECT_ROOT%&lt;/i&gt;). You can choose what's happen with existing files: Move, Copy or just do nothing.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Options:* Added the feature to select the path or set to default for Backup files. All Backup files will be moved and migrated in sub-folders, too.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Options:* Added the feature to select the path or set to default for BushTripInjector Database files. Your database files will be moved to the new location automatically. If you want to update the parking database, feel free to use your selected folder (Window &amp;rarr; Database) or copy it just into &lt;i&gt;%BTIHOME%&lt;/i&gt; and BushTripInjector will move it to correct location on startup.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Options:* Added the feature to select the path or set to default for other files. Those files and folders will be moved to new location.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Options:* Added the feature to select the path or set to default for MSFS compiler package output. Those files and folders will not be moved.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Options:* Added the feature to set to default log path. All existing log files will be moved to the new location.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Window Menu:* Added the menu items to open the folders for Project root, Backup, Database, Misc and config file.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Map Tile Cache:* Moved the map tile cache from &lt;i&gt;%BTIHOME%&lt;/i&gt; to &lt;i&gt;%LOCALAPPDATA%&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
UPDATE: *Aircraft:* Added some payware aircraft to BushTripInjector and MissionChanger: Just Flight PA28 Arrow III, PA28 Turbo Arrow III, PA28 Turbo Arrow IV and the MilViz 310R.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Sound files:* Fixed an issue with sound files, when a user has different sound files on TTS entries, but same text for the TTS. (thanks to Joanhoc)&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Map Tile Cache:* Fixed an issue with deleting outdated map tiles.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.2.5.2812 - World Update IX Italy/Malta&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* Updated the Airport and Runway Database included in BushTripInjector to WU9 Italy/Malta&lt;br&gt;Airport added: 322, changed 2862, deleted 5, Total 40153&lt;br&gt;Runway added: 746, changed 197, deleted 96, Total: 93982.&lt;br&gt;Details see db_changelog included in this package.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* Updated the Parking Database to to WU9 Italy/Malta&lt;br&gt;Parkings added: 3791, changed 1795, deleted 1568, Total 294470&lt;br&gt;This file is available as separate download on &lt;a href="https://flightsim.to/file/4131/bushtripinjector"&gt;BushTripInjector&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
UPDATE: *Online-Manual:* Added the manual for the Options-Sheet: &lt;a href="https://www.bushtripinjector.de/manual/sim-settings/"&gt;BushTripInjector Manual Options&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.2.5.2804 - File system restructure (Part I)&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; *Project Root Folder:*&lt;br&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Added the feature to select the root folder where BushTripInjector stores your projects (%PROJECT_ROOT%). By default, it remains to &lt;i&gt;%BTI_HOME%\PackageSource&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;When selecting a new folder, you will be asked if you want to copy, move or do nothing with your previous folder.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Learn more about the file system structure of BTI: &lt;a href="https://www.bushtripinjector.de/manual/filesystem/"&gt;BushTripInjector Manual Filesystem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; *Log Files:* &#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Added the possibility to select the log file folder, LogLevel, retention time and rolling mode on options screen.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Moved the default log file folder from &lt;i&gt;%BTI_HOME%&lt;/i&gt; to a sub folder &lt;i&gt;%BTI_HOME%\Logs&lt;/i&gt;. Existing log files will be moved automatically.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Log files will be removed automatically after a retention time. Default is 31 days&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; *Libraries:*&lt;br&gt;Moved the referenced and included DLLs of the package to a subfolder &lt;i&gt;Lib&lt;/i&gt;. BTI try to delete the old DLLs automatically.&lt;br&gt;Maybe your security software blocks BushTripInjector from deleting those libraries and you get some warnings or issues starting BTI. Please delete all DLL from &lt;i&gt;%BTI_HOME%&lt;/i&gt; by yourself.  &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *INI file:*&lt;br&gt;Migrated several project related entries of the INI file to BTI Fileformat.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
 *This Version has many changes in the core functionallity of BushTripInjector. Despite intensive testing, bugs and problems may occur. If you have an issue, please contact me on Discord: &lt;a href="http://discord.bushtripinjector.de/"&gt;discord.bushtripinjector.de&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;Thank you very much.*&#xD;
UPDATE: *Options:* Renamed the &lt;i&gt;Sim Settings&lt;/i&gt; Tab to &lt;i&gt;Options&lt;/i&gt; and moved it to the end.&#xD;
UPDATE: *DiscoveryFlights:* Fixed an issue preventing BTI to generate a DiscoveryFlight&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Sound files:* Fixed an issue with the migration of sound files to the new folder: Some files were detected as unused and moved/copied to orphaned.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Startup:* Fixed an issue with writing exception file on startup&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.2.4.2755&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Flight book:* The folder for saving the flight book has been changed to %MissionFolder%\AdditionalFiles\Documents (before: %BTIHOME%\Documents). No migration of already created flight books.&#xD;
UPDATE: *WebView2:* The WebView2 components have been updated to the latest version.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Internal:* Several optimizations and preparations for upcoming features.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Sound files:* Fixed an issue with the migration of sound files to the new folder when the user deleted this folder before migration &#xD;
BUGFIX: *Sound files:* Fixed an issue with the migration of sound files to the new folder when sound files with more than 260 chars were used.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Compiler:* Fixed an issue with a message box when the compiler couldn't create the mission.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.2.3.2743&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: Sound files &#xD;
FEATURE: The sound files work again for all legs after leaving the mission or trip.&lt;br&gt; _IMPORTANT:_ Your current files will be moved to &lt;i&gt;%MissionHome%\AdditionalFiles\Sound\&amp;ltBaseLanguageCode&amp;gt&lt;/i&gt;. Please backup your sound folder before opening your mission.&lt;br&gt;Migrated missions will not work with older versions of BushTripInjector with sound files until you remap those files in the older version.&#xD;
FEATURE: *Localized Sound files:* Use different sound files for each language for text-to-speech or InstructorDialogAction. Copy the wav-file into &lt;i&gt;%MissionHome%\AdditionalFiles\Sound\&amp;ltLanguageCode&amp;gt&lt;/i&gt; with the same filename. You will find more information at &lt;a href="https://www.bushtripinjector.de/manual/localized-soundfiles/"&gt;BushTripInjector Manual - Localized Sound Files&lt;/a&gt; &#xD;
&#xD;
 *This Version has many changes in the core functionallity of BushTripInjector. Despite intensive testing, bugs and problems may occur. If you have an issue, please contact me on Discord: &lt;a href="http://discord.bushtripinjector.de/"&gt;discord.bushtripinjector.de&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;Thank you very much.*&#xD;
&#xD;
UPDATE: *Select Sound* and *Create WAV* functions will create the files in &lt;i&gt;%MissionHome%\AdditionalFiles\Sound\&amp;ltBaseLanguageCode&amp;gt&lt;/i&gt;.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Soundfiles:* Only the sound files used are copied to the PackageFolder to reduce the size of the missions when uploading.&#xD;
UPDATE: *BushTrips:* Added a warning if the user does not use a BTI file for bush trips.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Online-Manual:* The manual has been extended by the localized sound files.: &lt;a href="https://www.bushtripinjector.de/manual/localized-soundfiles/"&gt;BushTripInjector Manual - Localized Sound Files&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
UPDATE: *Online-Manual:* Information about the file system and folder structure used and created by BushTripInjector has been added: &lt;a href="https://www.bushtripinjector.de/manual/filesystem/"&gt;BushTripInjector Manual Filesystem&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
UPDATE: *Cleanup:* Cleanup some parts of code.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *MessageBoxes:* Hopefully an issue with message boxes going distractingly into the background has been fixed.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.2.2.2716&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* Update of the internal airport and runway database to MSFS 1.25.7.0. Mainly minor changes in MagVar/Lat/Lon/Alt/Heading. For mission related changes like runway renaming see db_changelog in this package.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* The parking database has been updated to sim version 1.25.7.0. Please note that the parking database is a separate download.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Bgl-Reader:* Various adjustments to read the new BGL format that MSFS uses for generic airport BGLs.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Aircrafts:* Added *Carenado PA34T SENECA V* as Payware aircraft. Available for BushTripInjector and MissionChanger.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Translate-Window:* Fixed an issue with ColumnSize and Scrollbar in translate-window.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Translations* Fixed a problem when assigning translations to a waypoint if the waypoint identifier contains leading or trailing spaces.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.2.1.2700&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: Partial Missions&#xD;
PRO-VERSION: *Marketplace:* Removing whitespaces from image filenames for marketplace for SU9. If you are currently using images with blanks in the filenames, you need to remove and add them again!&#xD;
PRO-VERSION: *Marketplace:* Support for new Marketplace.json instead of business.json will follow. &#xD;
FEATURE: *Partial Missions:* Generate your legs as single bush trips for testing purposes. Keep in mind, such a cropped bush trip may behave differently if on previous legs payload/fuel or similar were changed.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Aircraft-Selection:* Added Beechcraft D17S Staggerwing (pgilbr)&#xD;
UPDATE: *Spb-Viewer:* Updated the property definitions to sim version 1.25.7.0&#xD;
UPDATE: *Aircraft-Selection:* Added a warning before generating a mission if the aircraft is not available in the simulator. (hoffa68)&#xD;
UPDATE: *Marketplace:* Updated ProjectTemplate and PackageTemplate for SU9.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Marketplace:* Mask more special characters in the description for the MarketPlace. (Synoxys)&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Event&amp;Triggers:* Fixed an issue that prevented the display of delay and speaker label for the InstructorDialog action.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Wait message:* Fixed an issue that you could edit the wait message. (Synoxys)&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Import Xml/Spb:* Fixed an issue on converting FSX-Simvars to MSFS-Simvars. (Synoxys)&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.2.0.2667&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: World Map Improvements&#xD;
FEATURE: *WorldMap:* Create text-to-speech with information from Wikipedia directly from WorldMap.&#xD;
FEATURE: *WorldMap:* Display the areas you created in Event&amp;Triggers on the WorldMap with pins.&#xD;
FEATURE: *WorldMap:* Display the TTS created by WorldMap on WorldMap with pins.&#xD;
FEATURE: *WorldMap:* Display the waypoints and stopover airports of your trip in WorldMap with pins.&#xD;
UPDATE: *WP-Names:* Remove leading and trailing spaces from waypoint names to avoid confusing the simulator.&#xD;
UPDATE: *TTS:* With a simupdate there was a change in the behavior of DelaySeconds for TTS. Previously the delay applied from the start of the action, now from the end of the action. This makes the automatic calculation of BushTripInjector unnecessary and it was therefore removed. Please check your TTS and the EnterDelay/ExitDelay there and reset it to a smaller value. &#xD;
BUGFIX: *BTI-File:* Fixed an issue where updating the copy of the LittleNavMap file contained in BTI did not work. This only affected if you deleted your LittleNavMap file and BTI used the internal copy. &#xD;
BUGFIX: *BTI-File:* Departure coordinates were not changed if the departure airport was changed and the new and old airport had an identically named parking position available.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *ProximityTrigger:* The reference to the ProximityTrigger has been removed from all areas when the ProximityTrigger is removed.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Aircrafts:* The installation status of a community aircraft was not detected correctly.&#xD;
</ChangeLog>
  <Downloadlink>https://flightsim.to/file/4131/bushtripinjector</Downloadlink>
  <RequiredDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>14</Minor>
    <Build>5</Build>
    <Revision>1</Revision>
  </RequiredDbVersion>
  <CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>25</Minor>
    <Build>9</Build>
    <Revision>1</Revision>
  </CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
</BushTripInjector>