<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BushTripInjector xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" Id="BushTripInjector">
  <MinVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>9</Minor>
    <Build>10</Build>
    <Revision>1612</Revision>
  </MinVersion>
  <PrevVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>10</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>-1</Revision>
  </PrevVersion>
  <CurrentVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>10</Minor>
    <Build>5</Build>
    <Revision>1814</Revision>
  </CurrentVersion>
  <ChangeLog>&lt;meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html;charset=UTF-8'&gt;&#xD;
0.10.5.1814&#xD;
FEATURE: *Event&amp;Triggers Editor:* Double click on an reference object will jump to this object in Event&amp;Triggers Editor.&#xD;
UPDATE: *FailureAction:* Added some new failures introduced by MSFS.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Trigger/Actions/Areas/WorldObject Id:* Updated the description id calculation, when the type of a Trigger/Action/Area/WorldObject is changed&#xD;
BUGFIX: *ObjectActivation/Counter/TimerActions:* Fixed an issue with removing triggers from these actions.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Actions Editor:* An issue with GUI refresh after a change in an action has been fixed.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *FailureAction:* Fixed the typo in "AttitudeIndicator".&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
0.10.4.1793&#xD;
UPDATE: *Airport &amp; Runway Database:*&lt;br&gt;Updated the internal database incl. new magnetic declination for airports with MSFS 1.20.6.0.&lt;br&gt;48 airports added&lt;br&gt;all airports changed because of new magnetic declination in SU6&lt;br&gt;8 airports removed.&lt;br&gt;Find a detailed list in db-changelog included in this package.&lt;br&gt;For each other location in the world, BushTripInjector is calculating the magnetic declination with the information from your sim (if detected).&#xD;
UPDATE: *Translate WP Names:*&lt;br&gt;Changed the default for new bush trips from "Translate" to "Non-translate" because of MSFS bug in SU6.&lt;br&gt;For existing bush trips you need to do this by yourself!&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
0.10.4.1784&#xD;
 *This is a major update. Some core functionality was touched. &lt;br&gt;Despite intensive testing, bugs and problems may occur. If you have an issue, please contact me on &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/fa6mtW2zz4"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;Thank you very much.*&#xD;
 *Fileformat-Change:* This version changed the internal fileformat to save triggers, actions and areas. Older version may no open those files, a backup will be created automatically.&#xD;
&#xD;
FEATURE: *Events &amp; Triggers Editor:* Reuse of Actions and Areas. Define actions and areas once and use them in different triggers and actions.&lt;br&gt;Known issues: Validation not working in all cases (red text).&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Loading tips:* Added an option to exclude the default loading tips from your trip (thanks to Koschi).&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Recent file list:* Increased the number of files in recent-file-list from 9 to 19.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Spb-Viewer:* Added properties for Reno Air Races, VR and some more.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Autopilot/Flightplan* Added some optimization for autopilot and flightplan. &#xD;
UPDATE: *Cruising Altitude:* Added a field to adjust the cruising altitude. Initial value from Little Navmap flightplan.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Event&amp;Triggers:* Optimized performance when handling proximity triggers with non-valid actions.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *MissionFailureAction:* Fixed an issue with the MissionFailureAction that prevents to be fired in some circumstances.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Airport-Creation:* Fixed an issue where you cannot finish the airport creation and stuck in creation wizard.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *2D-Image Creation:* Fixed an issue with zoom level on user defined airports.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Magnetic calculation:* Fixed a GUI glitch when calculated magnetic course &lt; 0° or &gt;360°&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Base data:* Fixed an glitch with Aircraft part on wide screens &#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
0.10.3.1742&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: Introducing Spell-Checking&#xD;
BushTripInjector will check your spelling for many input fields. You can enable this feature in Extra-Menu.&lt;br&gt;Basically, BTI uses the base language of the project. If a different language is detected in a field, this will be used.&lt;br&gt;The installed language packages of the operating system are required for this function, you may have to install them. &#xD;
&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Event &amp; Triggers:* Adding new triggers, actions and areas before current selected trigger, action or area.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Event &amp; Triggers:* Ordering triggers, actions and areas with drag and drop.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Shortcuts:* Added short-cuts for Open (Ctrl-O) and Save (Ctrl-S) into the GUI&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Aircraft-Position:* To place your aircraft on initial departure somewhere on the airport, remove runway and parking position and set the coordinates you want.&#xD;
FEATURE: *Event &amp; Triggers:* Help is now Data sensitive and forward you directly to selected trigger inside of Online-Help&#xD;
UPDATE: *Windows 11:* Added Windows 11 SDK support.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Flight book:* Integration of Online-Help into flight book functionality&#xD;
UPDATE: *Project name:* Check the no. of characters for the project name and give a warning on generation. Some users report issues with long project names: wrong legs in Sim, total loss of flight plan, detection of BushTrip end.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Mandatory WP / TTS:* Mandatory waypoints will use the rectangle areas from TTS and not vice versa!&#xD;
BUGFIX: *3D Image Generation:* Fixed an issue that leads to crash to desktop when clicking on Take-It!&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
0.10.2.1718&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: Introducing Context Sensitive Online-Help:&#xD;
Press F1 and you will get help about your current topic/window. Online-Help is currently available for many Menus, BaseData, WorldMap and some more. Growing rapidly in the background.&#xD;
 * _Many thanks go to the author of most help content: Frontech_*!&#xD;
I know, some things are still missing, but they will come with time. If you want to contribute, have suggestions for improvement or just find typos, please contact me.&#xD;
&#xD;
FEATURE: *Autoland Leg End:* For better testing, a feature was added to jump directly to the end of the leg and land on a runway of destination. You find this in 3D Image Generator Button &amp;quot;LandHere&amp;quot;.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Pilot/Copilot:* Select the Pilot and/or Copilot to be shown in your Aircraft. &#xD;
UPDATE: *Tante Ju:* Added the Junkers Ju52 to Aircraft selection.&#xD;
UPDATE: Changed the Distance and Heading field in flight plan tab to be in sync with internal game behavior.&#xD;
UPDATE: *3D Images:* Better calculation of ground level for Waypoints.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Sound files:* Added a check for valid sound files as MSFS documentation. Some sound files outside this specification will work, others will result in CTD. &#xD;
BUGFIX: *Sound files:* Duration of Sound files were not calculated. This could lead to abort the playback.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *flightsim.to:* Fixed an issue with multiple flightsim.to-links leading to CTD when clicking.&#xD;
BUGFIX: Fixed an issue with userpoints imported from LittleNavMap when initial load not finished.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
0.10.1.1690&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: Introducing Themes: &#xD;
 ' *Select your preferred Theme for BushTripInjector.*' &#xD;
 *Classic*, *Light* and *Dark* are available as a first version. &lt;br&gt;Known issues in Dark-Mode: HTML Windows like Update-Window&#xD;
&#xD;
UPDATE: *Translate-Window:* Extended column width&#xD;
UPDATE: Some more internal things to prepare upcoming features. Please report behavior or breaking changes with Areas in Event &amp; Triggers!&#xD;
UPDATE: Several small fixes, typos, ...&#xD;
&#xD;
</ChangeLog>
  <Downloadlink>https://flightsim.to/file/4131/bushtripinjector</Downloadlink>
  <RequiredDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>14</Minor>
    <Build>5</Build>
    <Revision>1</Revision>
  </RequiredDbVersion>
  <CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>20</Minor>
    <Build>6</Build>
    <Revision>0</Revision>
  </CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
</BushTripInjector>