<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BushTripInjector xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" Id="BushTripInjector">
  <MinVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>6</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>0</Revision>
  </MinVersion>
  <PrevVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>7</Minor>
    <Build>4</Build>
    <Revision>911</Revision>
  </PrevVersion>
  <CurrentVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>7</Minor>
    <Build>6</Build>
    <Revision>1027</Revision>
  </CurrentVersion>
  <ChangeLog>&#xD;
0.7.6.1027&#xD;
FEATURE: Selecting the Textcolors for Activity Widget&#xD;
FEATURE: Select the Language to use for WPNames and/or TTS, if you don*t want to use translated entries&#xD;
UPDATE: Another try to avoid spawning in other aircrafts when parking spots are used&#xD;
UPDATE: new window for update info&#xD;
UPDATE: Workaround for bing maps issue with antimeridian crossings&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
0.7.5.1008&#xD;
FEATURE: Activated Failures in Events&amp;Triggers Editor. Not all Failures will work with any plane. Checkout by yourself and blame Asobo/MS if not working, not me!&#xD;
Feel free to report working and non-working combinations, I will add them to the FAQ.&#xD;
FEATURE: Unintentional released the timer triggers in Event&amp;Triggers with v0.7.3.981. Complete Change-log here!&#xD;
FEATURE: Workaround for sim bug: Added the option to disable translation for Waypoint Names for displaying them in POI markers&#xD;
FEATURE: Workaround for bad TTS: Added the option to disable translation for TTS.&#xD;
UPDATE:  Create 2D Landing Images from WorldMap manually&#xD;
UPDATE:  Moved 'Add TTS' and 'Create Waypoint Image' into ContextMenu of WorldMap&#xD;
UPDATE:  Updated Property Definitions for SPB-Compiler to Sim Version 1.15.7&#xD;
BUGFIX:  Fixed a bug in creation of TTS for WayPoints after an airport. This could lead to not playing the TTS. You need to remove those TTS and re-create them, sorry! &#xD;
BUGFIX:  Fixed a bug drawing the TTS rectangle on WorldMap.&#xD;
</ChangeLog>
  <Downloadlink>https://flightsim.to/file/4131/bushtripinjector</Downloadlink>
  <RequiredDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>14</Minor>
    <Build>5</Build>
    <Revision>1</Revision>
  </RequiredDbVersion>
  <CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>15</Minor>
    <Build>7</Build>
    <Revision>0</Revision>
  </CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
</BushTripInjector>