<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BushTripInjector xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" Id="BushTripInjector">
  <MinVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>1</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>2375</Revision>
  </MinVersion>
  <PrevVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>1</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>-1</Revision>
  </PrevVersion>
  <CurrentVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>2</Minor>
    <Build>2</Build>
    <Revision>2716</Revision>
  </CurrentVersion>
  <ChangeLog>&lt;meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html;charset=UTF-8'&gt;&#xD;
1.2.2.2716&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* Update of the internal airport and runway database to MSFS 1.25.7.0. Mainly minor changes in MagVar/Lat/Lon/Alt/Heading. For mission related changes like runway renaming see db_changelog in this package.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* The parking database has been updated to sim version 1.25.7.0. Please note that the parking database is a separate download.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Bgl-Reader:* Various adjustments to read the new BGL format that MSFS uses for generic airport BGLs.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Aircrafts:* Added *Carenado PA34T SENECA V* as Payware aircraft. Available for BushTripInjector and MissionChanger.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Translate-Window:* Fixed an issue with ColumnSize and Scrollbar in translate-window.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Translations* Fixed a problem when assigning translations to a waypoint if the waypoint identifier contains leading or trailing spaces.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.2.1.2700&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: Partial Missions&#xD;
PRO-VERSION: *Marketplace:* Removing whitespaces from image filenames for marketplace for SU9. If you are currently using images with blanks in the filenames, you need to remove and add them again!&#xD;
PRO-VERSION: *Marketplace:* Support for new Marketplace.json instead of business.json will follow. &#xD;
FEATURE: *Partial Missions:* Generate your legs as single bush trips for testing purposes. Keep in mind, such a cropped bush trip may behave differently if on previous legs payload/fuel or similar were changed.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Aircraft-Selection:* Added Beechcraft D17S Staggerwing (pgilbr)&#xD;
UPDATE: *Spb-Viewer:* Updated the property definitions to sim version 1.25.7.0&#xD;
UPDATE: *Aircraft-Selection:* Added a warning before generating a mission if the aircraft is not available in the simulator. (hoffa68)&#xD;
UPDATE: *Marketplace:* Updated ProjectTemplate and PackageTemplate for SU9.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Marketplace:* Mask more special characters in the description for the MarketPlace. (Synoxys)&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Event&amp;Triggers:* Fixed an issue that prevented the display of delay and speaker label for the InstructorDialog action.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Wait message:* Fixed an issue that you could edit the wait message. (Synoxys)&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Import Xml/Spb:* Fixed an issue on converting FSX-Simvars to MSFS-Simvars. (Synoxys)&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.2.0.2667&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: World Map Improvements&#xD;
FEATURE: *WorldMap:* Create text-to-speech with information from Wikipedia directly from WorldMap.&#xD;
FEATURE: *WorldMap:* Display the areas you created in Event&amp;Triggers on the WorldMap with pins.&#xD;
FEATURE: *WorldMap:* Display the TTS created by WorldMap on WorldMap with pins.&#xD;
FEATURE: *WorldMap:* Display the waypoints and stopover airports of your trip in WorldMap with pins.&#xD;
UPDATE: *WP-Names:* Remove leading and trailing spaces from waypoint names to avoid confusing the simulator.&#xD;
UPDATE: *TTS:* With a simupdate there was a change in the behavior of DelaySeconds for TTS. Previously the delay applied from the start of the action, now from the end of the action. This makes the automatic calculation of BushTripInjector unnecessary and it was therefore removed. Please check your TTS and the EnterDelay/ExitDelay there and reset it to a smaller value. &#xD;
BUGFIX: *BTI-File:* Fixed an issue where updating the copy of the LittleNavMap file contained in BTI did not work. This only affected if you deleted your LittleNavMap file and BTI used the internal copy. &#xD;
BUGFIX: *BTI-File:* Departure coordinates were not changed if the departure airport was changed and the new and old airport had an identically named parking position available.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *ProximityTrigger:* The reference to the ProximityTrigger has been removed from all areas when the ProximityTrigger is removed.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Aircrafts:* The installation status of a community aircraft was not detected correctly.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.7.2635&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Flight book:* Add the TTS you have defined from Worldmap to the flight book. Auto-detect the leg and export the associated TTS in flight plan order. (FronTech)&#xD;
UPDATE: *WorldMap:* The world map options have been moved to an expander in the upper right corner to be prepared for future developments.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Read-LNM:* Remove line feeds from names and ids to avoid empty navigation logs.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Wiki:* Show wikilinks of other languages sorted alphabetically.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Wiki:* Remember the Window position and size.&#xD;
UPDATE: *WebView2:* Updated to latest version of WebView2&#xD;
UPDATE: *OpenXml:* Updated to latest version of OpenXml DocumentFormat&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Wiki:* English wiki link was mapped to base-lng and opened the wrong wiki when using a base-lng other than en-US.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *CreateImages:* An issue with creating images from non-Microsoft map providers has been fixed. (Thx to FronTech)&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.6.2590&#xD;
FEATURE: *Open closed Airports:* Open closed airports: Added the ability to reopen airports closed in the simulation. Check the flight plan page! BushTripInjector will notify you when your flight plan contains a closed airport.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *HTML Tagging:* Changed the tagging of &amp;amp; &amp;apos; &amp;quot; in the description field has been changed when this text is defined only once. Due to a simulation error, they are not displayed correctly for custom content when HTLM tags are used. You can check the usage in the translation window.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* several improvements to find closed airports as the sim does. New database with 288 airports now closed and 177 airfields now marked as open. Details as always in the additional db-changelog.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Pre-flight check:* Check if an airport used in the mission is closed and issue a corresponding message.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Refueling Airports:* closed airports are now not used as refueling airports.&#xD;
UPDATE: *AircraftSelection:* Shows the installation status of aircraft. BTI shows you all aircraft with the status, MissionChanger only the installed ones.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Aircrafts:* Added the Dornier DoJ series&#xD;
UPDATE: *Aircrafts:* Added the Fokker FVII series&#xD;
UPDATE: *Aircrafts:* Added the Carenado M20R series&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.5.2563&#xD;
BUGFIX: *CTD:* Fixed an issue on startup, when your flightplan contains converted waypoints to airports&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.5.2552&#xD;
UPDATE: *Aircraft &amp; Livery Handling:* Better selection of aircraft in BaseData. Display of Official, Premium/Deluxe, Payware and Community Aircrafts and Liveries in a tree view.&lt;br&gt;Information about MSFS Marketplace encrypted planes are now read from the cloud at launch. *If you would like me to include your payware, please contact me on Discord.* I can then add these without you needing a new version of the BTI&#xD;
UPDATE: *DeepL-API:* Several improvements including a pre-translation word count and an information about quota exceeds or when the available chars go less than 10% after translation.&#xD;
UPDATE: *WorldMap:* Closed airports are crossed out now.&#xD;
UPDATE: *WorldMap:* The TTS creation from the WorldMap can now be canceled and uses the click point.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Translations:* A CTD was fixed when an issue occurred during automatic translation.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.4.2526&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: World Update 8 - Iberia&#xD;
UPDATE: *Main-Database:* Updated the internal database to sim version 1.24.5.0. Airports increased by 982, runways by 2000. For details, see db-changelog.txt included in this package.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Parking-Database:* Updated the parking database to sim version 1.24.5.0. Increased by 6342 parking spots. Please keep in mind, the parking database is a separate download.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Spb-Viewer:* Updated the Property-Definitions to Sim 1.24.5.0&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.4.2519&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: World Update 8 - Iberia&#xD;
UPDATE: *Language:* Added pt-PT as supported language in BTI. Bem-vindo a Portugal.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* New databases are delayed for 2-3 days. My BGL-Reader is broken after WU8, I need to fix it first. &#xD;
UPDATE: *Modify Airport:* Added the option to cancel and revert the changes.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Create Airport:* Added the option to override existing airports.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Flightsim.to:* Adjustments to new flightsim.to add-on download format.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.3.2500&#xD;
USER-REQ: *KML-Export:* Export your Flightplan as KML to open it in Google Earth or any other tool of your choice.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Extra-Menu:* The "Clear Message Cache" item has been renamed to "Reset All Messages" for clarity.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Spb-Viewer:* Updated the Property-Definitions to Sim 1.23.12.0&#xD;
BUGFIX: *ModelLibBrowser:* Fixed an issue that prevented the ModelLibBrowser from opening (thanks FronTech).&#xD;
BUGFIX: *ModelLibBrowser:* Fixed an issue that prevented ModelLibBrowser from displaying the already loaded models.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Startup Handling:* Added sync of threads at startup to avoid clicks on the GUI before the GUI is ready to process clicks.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Images:* Fixed an issue when creating content info thumbnails with incorrect image sizes.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Airport-File:* The custom airport is no longer saved in a separate file when using the BTI file format.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.2.2476&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Dependencies:* Define Dependencies to other packages. This feature is only available when using BTI Fileformat. You will find the Name and Version in the manifest of the used package. Versions are detected automatically. Dependencies of those dependencies will be added automatically in most cases.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* Updated internal database for airports and runway to Sim Version 1.23.12.0 Sim Update 8. Several changes in elevation and magnetic declination. Some runways have therefore been renamed.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* Updated the parking database package again.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Steam:* Better message when BTI couldn't compile the mission with link to manual.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *TTS:* Fixed a CTD in TTS Window.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.1.2460&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Dark mode:* An issue in dark mode with CTD at startup has been fixed.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Translate:* Fixed an issue with the translation window when trip fails to compile&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Change language:* Fixed an issue when changing the project language if trip cannot be compiled&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Flight Log:* An issue with creating the flight log has been fixed when trip cannot be compiled&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.1.2442&#xD;
PRO-VERSION: *MediaSlider/MediaScroller:*&lt;br&gt;Added the option to add images for marketplace MediaSlider and Media Scroller. This feature is only available when using BTI Fileformat.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Flight book:* Added the option to include the DialogAction and InstructorDialogAction texts for ProximityTriggers bound to areas on waypoints. Thanks to FronTech.&#xD;
UPDATE: *WebView2:* Updated the WebView2 components to most recent version.&lt;br&gt; *Please delete the "runtimes" folder in your BushTripInjector-Installation.*&#xD;
UPDATE: *Refuel:* Check for Gas-Stations in Parking-Database and not only for the fuel-flags in airport definition. MSFS doesn't have correct fuel-flags for many small airports.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Translation-Window:* Added a notification about not applied data when closing the window via cancel or the X in the title bar.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Translation:* Better handling of non-supported languages of DeepL-API.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Translation:* Performance optimizations. &#xD;
BUGFIX: *SaveAs:* However, the *Save As* menu was not visible for everyone (Thanks Koschi).&#xD;
BUGFIX: *3D Image Generator:* Fixed an issue prevents starting 3D Image Generator when using a flightplan without airports. (Thanks bhpowell)&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Load Mission:* Fixed an issue loading the mission when a BTI converted airport with a starting runway with a true heading between 0 and 10 was selected. (Thanks bhpowell)&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Basedata:* The slipped "Change - Project - Language" button has been moved to the right place again&#xD;
BUGFIX: *LicenseRequest:* Fixed an issue where the text file could not be created.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Anti-Meridian-Crossings:* Fixed an issue with refueling airports when your trip crosses the anti-meridian.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.1.0.2376&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* Updated internal airport and runway database to sim version 1.22.2.0. 622 added airports, 56 deleted airports. 1414 new runways, 196 runways removed. Details see db_changelog.txt included in this package.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database:* Also the park database has been updated to sim version 1.22.2.0. Please note that this is a separate file for download. &#xD;
UPDATE: *AirportCreation:* Calculation of magnetic declination when creating airports. For already created airports, magnetic declination is only calculated if it is not currently set.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Parking-Db:* Fixed an issue when checking for parking database updates.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *AirportCreation:* Fixed an issue with the creation of airports: Runways did not reach the internal database correctly. This resulted in invalid airports in your mission. We apologize for this. Thanks to Brad Allen for pointing this out.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *CTD:* Fixed an issue where BTI can crash to desktop if no runway surface can be detected.&#xD;
</ChangeLog>
  <Downloadlink>https://flightsim.to/file/4131/bushtripinjector</Downloadlink>
  <RequiredDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>14</Minor>
    <Build>5</Build>
    <Revision>1</Revision>
  </RequiredDbVersion>
  <CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>25</Minor>
    <Build>7</Build>
    <Revision>0</Revision>
  </CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
</BushTripInjector>