<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BushTripInjector xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" Id="BushTripInjector">
  <MinVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>10</Minor>
    <Build>3</Build>
    <Revision>1742</Revision>
  </MinVersion>
  <PrevVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>0</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>-1</Revision>
  </PrevVersion>
  <CurrentVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>0</Minor>
    <Build>6</Build>
    <Revision>2198</Revision>
  </CurrentVersion>
  <ChangeLog>&lt;meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html;charset=UTF-8'&gt;&#xD;
1.0.6.2198&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: Resampling Audio-Files, Save-As, Database-Viewer, Backups&#xD;
Pro-Version: After compiling a trip, an export.zip is generated in your project folder, if you enabled "Compile to Project-Folder".&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Compile:* For better marketplace handling, compile your bush trip into your project folder instead of global package folder. You can enable or disable this on Sim-Settings-Tab&#xD;
FEATURE: *Resampling Audio-Files:* Resampling and convert audio files to MSFS recommended format (wav, 22Khz, 16bit, mono). Supported Input formats: mp3, wav, wma, aiff and aac!&#xD;
FEATURE: *SaveAs:* Save your current mission in another file. Keep in mind, the project name and output is not changed and you need to do this by yourself.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Database-Viewer:* Show the version of the database and the parking database, if present.&#xD;
UPDATE: *GUI:* A small redesign of data tables in classic theme. &#xD;
UPDATE: *Messages*: Improved several messages to avoid user confusion.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Backup:* Creates a daily backup of bushtripinjector.ini and other saved files in %BTIHOME%\BushTripInjector_SAVES\Backup&#xD;
UPDATE: *Backup:* Change the location for backups of Little Nav Map or BushTripInjector Source files to %BTIHOME%\BushTripInjector_SAVES\Backup&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Scaling/Textscaling:* Fixed an issue when you are using display scaling and in addition a text scaling in windows for some dialogs incl. die License-Key dialog. (Thanks to OzzyKym) &#xD;
BUGFIX: Fixed an issue deleting and copying files from/to community folder or deleting from mission saves folder.&#xD;
BUGFIX: Fixed an issue creating the installer packages.&#xD;
BUGFIX: Fixed an issue with read-only files in packages-folder. &#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.0.5.2154&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: Wav-Recording, Database-Viewer&#xD;
FEATURE: *WAV-Recording:* Record your own wav-files from all of your input and output devices.&#xD;
FEATURE: *Database-Viewer:* Show, sort, filter the BushTripInjector's internal airport, runway and parking database. Show the airports with a single click on the map.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Sound files:* Sound files stopped working again after leaving the bush trips. Therefore, the warning message is active again.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Text-to-speech:* Added online manual content and enabled the *F1*-key function.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Create WAV:* Added online manual content and enabled the *F1*-key function.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Landmarks:* Removed an unnecessary message when no landmarks are present when loading a mission.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.0.4.2134&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: Wikipedia in BaseLanguage, WAV-File Creation from TTS&#xD;
&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Wikipedia Texts from Wikipedia of your base language.* The Wikipedia texts are now determined from the base language set in BushTripInjector. If this is not English (en-GB or en-US), check your Wiki texts. For compatibility reasons, en.wikipedia.org is still the Wikipedia to search, but the local entries linked there will be displayed. If an entry is not available there, the English article will still be used.&lt;br&gt;If there is an entry in the local Wikipedia that is not available in en.wikipedia.org, fell free to create an article on en.wikipedia.org and set a link to the language wiki. Wikipedia lives from and for everyone and can be maintained by everyone.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *WAV-Files:* Create WAV Files from TTS and Event&amp;Triggers Editor. Select your preferred voice, or let BTI decide by Language, Gender and Age. If you are missing some voices, a step-by-step documentation to activate all windows voices is vailable on &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Windows10/comments/96dx8z/how_unlock_all_windows_10_hidden_tts_voices_for/" title="Reddit"&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
UPDATE: *IngameMarker breaks bush trips:* Unfortunately, ingame markers prevent bush trips from being saved correctly in the simulator at the end of a leg and the trip cannot be continued. A restart from the beginning would be necessary. BTI now issues appropriate warnings and in some cases prevents the creation of ingame markers. &#xD;
 * _Apologies to any users affected by this issue for not noticing this during development, alpha or preview testing._*&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Wiki:* Show Wikipedia in your Browser for all available languages from Wiki-Window. Click right-button on your mouse to show the available wikis. (rug4ever)&#xD;
USER-REQ: *IngameMarker:* When creating IngameMarker from Landmark page, no more direction pointer will be generated because you cannot deativate them. To use this functionallity, please use the Event&amp;Triggers Editor. (DiscoveryFlights)&#xD;
FEATURE: *Landmarks:* Generate IngameMarkers and associated ObjectActivations for Event&amp;Triggers Editor from Landmark Tab.&lt;br&gt;The IngameMarker is deactivated by Default, use the ObjectActivation to activate it where ever you want.&lt;br&gt;Keep in mind, if you don't activate them by yourself, they are not visible ingame. (DiscoveryFlight)&#xD;
UPDATE: *Landmarks:* Show a warning message if landmarks are used in a bush trip.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Landmarks:* When using Landmarks as IngameMarker, set the description type to distance, if description has less than 3 chars. (DiscoveryFlight)&#xD;
UPDATE: *Performance:* Massive increase of performance when using refueling options with many legs/waypoints.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Leg2+:* Added the Leg2+ workaround for IngameMarker, too.&#xD;
UPDATE: *New-Dialog:* Added missing tooltips and "F1-Key" help.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Spb-Viewer*: Restore Window Positions.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Landmarks:* Bring back the possibility to sort for the flags.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.0.3.2095&#xD;
FEATURE: *WorldMap:* Copy the coordinates in different formats to Clipboard  for use in Google Maps, Bing Maps or just BushTripInjector.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Window-Menu:* Show/Jump to Sounds folder, BushTripInjector File and Little Navmap File.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Helpmenu:* Added entries for Support channel, Manual, Homepage and Project page on flightsim.to&#xD;
UPDATE: *IngameMarkers:* Choose the Color of the Maintext&#xD;
UPDATE: *IngameMarkers:* Choose if you want to display your entered text, the distance to the POI or the altitude of the POI.&#xD;
UPDATE: *IngameMarkers:* Added the AltitudeText with same features as SecondaryText.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Paste coordinates:* Convert different formats (DEC, DMS, MSFS, ...) when pasting coordinates in Areas, WorldObjects, Triggers, ...&#xD;
UPDATE: *BingMapsAPI:* The BingMaps API has currently issues in the northern part of France. Ignoring these errors from WorldMap now. *Attention:* Creating Landmarks or other objects can have a wrong elevation/altitude. Check the statusbar!&#xD;
UPDATE: *Flightsim.to:* Better handling to hide in DiscoveryFlights.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *LibraryObject:* Added the missing Activate-flag into GUI.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.0.2.2064&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: IngameMarker&#xD;
Define your own ingame markers. Position them over areas, waypoints or landmarks. Choose whether you want to have a direction indicator or not. Or just create the IngameMarkers in a predefined way from the landmarks.&lt;br&gt;IngameMarkers are visible independent from Sim Settings or external landmarks and shown in BushTrips. &#xD;
&#xD;
USER-REQ: *DialogAction/TTS:* Choose between the different speakers: Narrator, Co-Pilot and Instructor.&#xD;
FEATURE: *ProjectFiles:* Second step for Project Handling:&lt;br&gt;Single File Store for BushTrips created via File&gt;New to get rid of the INI-File and SAVES Folder.&#xD;
FEATURE: *WeatherFile:* Restore missing weather file, if it is not present on origin from project file.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Soundfiles:* Removed the warning when adding sound files because they are working with BTI since 0.10.9.1946.&#xD;
UPDATE: *WAV-Files:* Check WAV Files for bits per sample. MSFS supports max. 16 bits per sample.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Check for Save:* Added the missing message for saving current mission when closing the app via File &gt; Exit.&#xD;
UPDATE: *CruisingAltitude:* Added Cruising Altitude to DiscoveryFlights.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Landmarks:* Better handling of the CheckBox for Activate and IngameMarker&#xD;
UPDATE: *Paste LLA:* Fixed an issue pasting LatLonAlt not working for WorldObjects.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *LegCompletion-TTS:* Fixed an issue with Leg completion TTS not spoken when using Mandatory Waypoints.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *MapLayer:* Fixed an issue that with BushTrips the MapLayer for DiscoveryFlights remained active.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Event&amp;Triggers:* Fixed an issue with world objects not compiling when no triggers were present.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Mandatory Waypoints:* Hopefully fixed an issue with Multithreading and synchronizing back when creating the triggers and actions for mandatory waypoints. Please report if the issue is still present.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *IngameMarker/PointOfInterest:* Fixed an issue saving the text for IngameMarkers and PointOfInterest.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Event&amp;Triggers:* Fixed an CTD when removing a ProximityTrigger.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Misc.:* Fixed several minor issues (Theme not applied, wrong message box format, ...)&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.0.1.2020&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: RandomAction, Bugfixes for Discovery&#xD;
FEATURE: *RandomAction:* Added the RandomAction to Events&amp;Triggers Editor for BushTrips and DiscoveryFlights.&lt;br&gt;Use the RandomActions to give the user more variation. Activate sceneries in the vicinity, simulate nature spectacles or simply let animals run in random directions. There are no limits to your creativity.&#xD;
UPDATE: *OpenFileDialog:* Changed the default file filter to all supported file formats.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Discovery:* Handle menu items for DiscoveryFlights. *Please check your current settings after loading DiscoveryFlights.*&#xD;
UPDATE: *MarketPlace:* Added marketplace handling for DiscoveryFlights. &#xD;
UPDATE: *Import XML/SPB:* Added several properties to Import-Parser: DefaultActivated (all triggers), OnScreenTimer (TimerTrigger).&#xD;
UPDATE: *XamlBehaviors:* Updated component to most recent version.&#xD;
UPDATE: *WebView2:* Updated component to most recent version. Several fixes. &#xD;
UPDATE: *ProjectFile:* Save the Weather-file inside of the project-file.&#xD;
UPDATE: *LibraryObject*:  More accurate positioning of objects (6.78cm resolution at equator). (thx goes to Synoxys)&#xD;
UPDATE: *Areas*:  More accurate positioning of areas for Rectangle, Cylinder, Teleport and Landmarks (6.78cm resolution at equator). (thx goes to Synoxys)&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Discovery:* Fixed an issue on generating DicoveryFlights when no translation is present.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Discovery:* Fixed some issues loading the saved vaules in some conditions (Weather, Colors, Menu, Translate...). &#xD;
BUGFIX: *Discovery:* Several small fixes and optimizations for DiscoveryFlight.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.0.0.1994&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: DiscoveryFlights&#xD;
Unlocking the DiscoveryFlights for all users. This was made possible by the kind permission and waiver of exclusive rights of a customer on the US West Coast.&lt;br&gt;Create DiscoveryFlights and tell us more about a region. Define landmarks to make users aware of them. Use the Events&amp;Triggers editor to give the user more visual and audible impressions. Choose the music style and volume when approaching a POI. And much more.&#xD;
&#xD;
This Version has many changes in the core functionallity of BushTripInjector because of merging some branches into community version.&lt;br&gt;Despite intensive testing, bugs and problems may occur. If you have an issue, please contact me on &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/fa6mtW2zz4"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;Thank you very much.&#xD;
&#xD;
USER-REQ: Hide the MainWindow while taking images with 3d Image Generator. (Koschi)&#xD;
USER-REQ: Added a checkbox to worldmap sheet to show/hide only selected flightsim.to add-ons. (FronTech)&#xD;
FEATURE: *ProjectFiles:* Save your Mission with all information in a single file (only available for DiscoversFlights yet).&#xD;
FEATURE: *WorldMap:* Added an option to show pins for landmarks on WorldMap. The tooltip of the pin shows you the name of the landmark.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Areas:* Added the AltitudeIsAGL flag to CylinderArea and RectangleArea. Available in Import XML/SPB Module, too.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Waiting Screen:* A waiting screen has been added so as not to inconvenience the users when it takes longer than usual&#xD;
UPDATE: *Typos* As usual, some typos corrected. (Thanks to ProfSC)&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Leg2+:* Fixed an issue when the ProximityTriggers has different Activated/Deactivated Flags.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Leg2+:* Added the Leg2+ workaround for Property-, Airportlanding-, AreaLanding-, Counter- and TimerTrigger, too.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *CruisingAlt:* Fixed an issue with CruisingAlt was not set correctly (BushTrip &amp; Discovery)&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Changelog:* Fixed an issue when viewing the changelog from helpmenu and no parking database is installed.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
</ChangeLog>
  <Downloadlink>https://flightsim.to/file/4131/bushtripinjector</Downloadlink>
  <RequiredDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>14</Minor>
    <Build>5</Build>
    <Revision>1</Revision>
  </RequiredDbVersion>
  <CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>21</Minor>
    <Build>13</Build>
    <Revision>0</Revision>
  </CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
</BushTripInjector>