<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BushTripInjector xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" Id="BushTripInjector">
  <MinVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>7</Minor>
    <Build>7</Build>
    <Revision>1046</Revision>
  </MinVersion>
  <PrevVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>8</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>-1</Revision>
  </PrevVersion>
  <CurrentVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>8</Minor>
    <Build>4</Build>
    <Revision>1207</Revision>
  </CurrentVersion>
  <ChangeLog>&#xD;
0.8.4.1207&#xD;
FEATURE: Activated the *CounterTriggers* in Event&amp;Triggers Editor: Will be fired when reaching the Counter. Increase or Decrease the Counter with CountAction&#xD;
FEATURE: Activated the *CountAction* in Event&amp;Triggers Editor: Increase or Decrease the count of a CounterTrigger.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Updated the internal airport and runway database to Sim-Version 1.16.2.0*: &lt;br&gt;185 Airports added, 127 changed, 2 deleted (HSMY / LEDS) &lt;br&gt;410 new runways, 20 changes and 32 deleted runways. &lt;br&gt;Details see "db-changelog-1.15.8.0--1.16.2.0.txt".&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed an bug in AdjustElevation function when waypoint has an elevation of zero&#xD;
UPDATE: Added the DelaySeconds to Event&amp;Triggers GUI for TTS.&#xD;
UPDATE: Deactivated the code for soundfiles fix announced for 1.16.2.0. It did not find the way to the sim&#xD;
UPDATE: Adaption of TTS to Sim changes introduced with 1.16.2.0, which prevented the translated texts from being read. &#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
0.8.3.1192&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed a bug that prevented saving the acceptance of the EULA&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
0.8.3.1188&#xD;
UPDATE: *Modifications for Sim 1.16.2.0 to compile without errors about MarketplaceData and business.json* . But also with the errors, the trip was working!&#xD;
UPDATE: *Compatibility with XBOX Version.* &#xD;
USER-REQ: Added a function to remove obsolete images from images-folder (Pennsocke)&#xD;
FEATURE: Added the AdjustTimerAction to Event&amp;Triggers Editor: Increase or Decrease the time of a TimerTrigger&#xD;
FEATURE: Added the ResetTimerAction to Event&amp;Triggers Editor: Reset the time of a TimerTrigger&#xD;
FEATURE: Added the InstructorDialog to Event&amp;Triggers Editor: Display and play dialog in the adventure window.&#xD;
UPDATE: Accepting the EULA is now mandatory.&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed a bug with horizontal scrolling in TTS Window (thanks to Koschi)&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed a bug, Elevations of Waypoints were not calculated after loading a plan.&#xD;
UPDATE: Hidden feature for a good friend :)&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
0.8.2.1149&#xD;
FEATURE: Activated the ObjectActivationAction in Event&amp;Triggers. Activate or deactivate other triggers depending on Conditions, Timers, Areas.&#xD;
FEATURE: For each Trigger in E&amp;T Editor, you can select whether the trigger can be fired once or more&#xD;
USER-REQ: Added a flag to set MultiPlayer in the flt-file&#xD;
UPDATE: Workaround for sound files. Fix for announced change in sim-beta, unfortunately the fix is not included in most recent sim-beta. &#xD;
UPDATE: Some GUI optimizations for the Event&amp;Triggers Editor&#xD;
UPDATE: Tons of Tooltips&#xD;
UPDATE: Validate the triggers before generating a BushTrip.&#xD;
TEASER: Implemented some more triggers and actions for selected testers. *Be curious what else is in store for you.*&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
0.8.1.1117&#xD;
 'USER-REQ: Added the feature to convert first or last waypoint to an airport.' &#xD;
&#xD;
FEATURE: Enhanced the Events&amp;Triggers Editor to change AssistancePreset inflight.&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed an issue when creating TTS for first waypoints of a leg. You need to re-create those TTS, not only the trip, I'm sorry!&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed an issue with the elevation of the runway startpoints on user-airports.&#xD;
UPDATE: Calculate airport boundaries as the sim calculates them for display in Worldmap&#xD;
UPDATE: Apptitle not updated on changes sometimes&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
0.8.0.1092&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: Unlocking the Secret of 'AssistancePresets'!&#xD;
 *Your Controls:* BushTripInjector gives you the control over all assistance options. It is your choice which settings are set and whether they should be unlocked for the user.&#xD;
Attention: Not all combination could be testet, some of the settings may not work or break the BushTrip. Please check your desired settings with your trip.&#xD;
&#xD;
USER-REQ: Paste Coords from Google Maps (and others) into Landmarks-Dialog (koschi)&#xD;
USER-REQ: Determinate the Altitude of Landmark in Landmarkwindow.&#xD;
UPDATE: New Runway Surfaces for Airport Creation: FOREST, GRASS_BUMPY, HARD_TURF, LONG_GRASS, SHORT_GRASS, URBAN and WRIGHT_FLYER_TRACK&#xD;
UPDATE: Fixed another thing for crazy steam installations (seems to be steam fix weeks again)&#xD;
UPDATE: *Some better Map REST-API Handling to investigate an issue with expired SessionIds.*&#xD;
</ChangeLog>
  <Downloadlink>https://flightsim.to/file/4131/bushtripinjector</Downloadlink>
  <RequiredDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>14</Minor>
    <Build>5</Build>
    <Revision>1</Revision>
  </RequiredDbVersion>
  <CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>16</Minor>
    <Build>2</Build>
    <Revision>0</Revision>
  </CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
</BushTripInjector>
