<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BushTripInjector xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" Id="BushTripInjector">
  <MinVersion>
    <Major>3</Major>
    <Minor>4</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>4634</Revision>
  </MinVersion>
  <PrevVersion>
    <Major>3</Major>
    <Minor>4</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>-1</Revision>
  </PrevVersion>
  <CurrentVersion>
    <Major>4</Major>
    <Minor>3</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>4866</Revision>
  </CurrentVersion>
  <ChangeLog>&lt;meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html;charset=UTF-8'&gt;&#xD;
4.3.0.4866 - Microsoft Flightsimulator 2024 Part V&#xD;
This Version has many changes in the core functionality of BushTripInjector. Despite intensive testing, bugs and problems may occur.&#xD;
If you have an issue, please contact me on Discord: BushTripInjector Discord. Thank you very much.&#xD;
&#xD;
 'Features:'&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Intersections:* Add the ICAO Airport to Intersections (named/unnamed waypoints, RNAV, ...) in PLN file when navaid database is installed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Intersections:* Choose whether Intersections should always be changed to User-WP, or if they do not exist, or not at all.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *User-WP:* The option to choose whether the ident should be added to the user waypoints has been added.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt; &#xD;
&#xD;
 'Updates:'&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *PLN Generation:* Several changes in the generated PLN file for better GPS handling in MSFS2020 and MSFS2024.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Covers:* Removed some unnecessary entries in the BTI file when no covers were set.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Preflight-Check:* A check has been added to validate if an intersection waypoint is included in the navigation database.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&#xD;
 'Fixes:'&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Generate-Submission:* Fixed an issue where creating sub-missions for MSFS 2024 would select the wrong simulator. &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Covers:* An issue with the visibility of the cover options in non-bush trip missions has been fixed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
4.2.0.4844 - Microsoft Flightsimulator 2024 Part IV&#xD;
 'Features:'&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Aircrafts:* Reading the list of installed aircraft and liveries from MSFS 2024. Note that using a livery will not work due to a bug in MSFS 2024.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Covers:* Added the possibility to define the covers to be mounted on the aircraft before the flight.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt; &#xD;
&#xD;
 'Updates:'&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Preflight-Check:* A warning has been added to the preflight check if the title can presumably not be displayed completely in MSFS 2024.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *3D Image Generation:* Added the option to start MSFS 2020 and MSFS 2024.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Aircrafts&amp;Liveries:* Added UI output when reading aircraft and liveries.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Aircrafts&amp;Liveries:* The aircraft mapping has been moved from the aircraft database to a separate file on Github: &lt;a href="https://github.com/BuffyGC/BushTripInjector/blob/main/api/v1/aircrafts/aircraftmapping.xml"&gt;Aircraft Mapping on Github&lt;/a&gt;. Contribute by creating a branch, adding the mapping and creating a pull request. I'll review it and then merge the PR.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *License-Checks:* Added *www.* prefix to all license check calls to avoid redirecting from the server and speed up the query.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *License-Checks:* To speed up the query, all calls to the licence check have been moved to a different endpoint.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Databases:* Updated the databases to AIRAC 2413. Please note: About 10% of the VOR/NDB has been removed. Please check your Usage-Db!&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *SimConnect:* Updated to MSFS2024 SDK 1.1.2&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *SimWatcher:* Added the functionality for MSFS 2024&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&#xD;
 'Fixes:'&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Landmarks:* Fixed an issue that prevented the creation of IGM in Event &amp; Trigger from the Landmarks sheet.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
4.1.1.4805 - Microsoft Flightsimulator 2024 Part III: MSFS2024 Release&#xD;
 'Updates:'&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *User-Interface:* Some restructuring of the menu. I would appreciate feedback on Discord.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Aircrafts:* The option to link between MSFS2020 and MSFS2024 aircraft names has been added internally. You can contribute by adding the *Name2024* attribute to an aircraft in the list of aircrafts on Github: &lt;a href="https://github.com/BuffyGC/BushTripInjector/blob/main/api/v1/aircrafts/aircrafts.xml"&gt;Aircraftlist on Github&lt;/a&gt;. See the Baron G58 for an example. For these changes to take effect, you must reload the list via *Extras* &amp;rarr; *Load Liveries/Aircrafts*&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *PropertyDefinitions:* Updated to MSFS2024 1.1.7.0&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *SimConnect:* Updated to MSFS2024 SDK 1.0.0&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Maintenance:* Some minor stability changes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
4.1.0.4790 - Microsoft Flightsimulator 2024 Part II&#xD;
 'Fixes:'&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Start-Up:* Fixed a CTD on Startup with a strange combination of MSFS2020 and MSFS2024 installations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Sim-Detection:* Fixed some minor issues detecting MSFS2024 with Steam and Store/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Sim-Detection:* Fixed an issue detecting MSFS2020 with Steam/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Options:* An issue with overlapping fields in the options sheet has been fixed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
 'Features:'&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Bundles:* Added basic support for Bundles with Flightsimulator 2024&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *SPB-Decompiler:* The option to decode MSFS 2024 SimPropBinary files (*.spb) has been added.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
 'Updates:'&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt; *Bundles:* Invalid packages and packages with different simulator versions can be recreated when the bundle is generated&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
4.0.0.4771 - Microsoft Flightsimulator 2024&#xD;
 *Basic version to support generation and compilation of MSFS 2024 Bush Trips, Landing Challenges and Discover Flights*&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Detect Microsoft Flightsimulator 2024 Store-Version&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Detect Microsoft Flightsimulator 2024 Steam-Version&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Configuration for compiling missions with SDK or without SDK&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Start MSFS 2024 via App Invoker for MS Store Version with Faststart Option&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Start MSFS 2024 via Steam App Invoker or FlightSimulator.exe for Steam Version with Faststart Option&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Create new User-Xml-Files for Missions when generating for MSFS 2024&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Adjustments for the manifest.json in MSFS 2024&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Several adjustments in Windows and Menus&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Updated to SimConnect 2024&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Simulator version added to the user database for future use&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&#xD;
 *Things that have not yet been implemented, but would be required for smooth operation with MSFS 2024:*&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Marketplace changes for MSFS 2024&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;s&gt;SPB Decompiler for MSFS 2024&lt;/s&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Xml-Importer for MSFS 2024&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;MSFS 2024 Database Handling&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;MSFS 2024 POI Handling&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Aircraft and Livery Support for MSFS 2024&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Dependency Handling&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Magnetic Declination for MSFS 2024&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;Different Usage Database for MSFS 2024&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;and much more, ...&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&#xD;
 *other changes and fixes:*&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;UPDATE: *PropDefs:* Updated to the most recent Property Definitions of MSFS2020 to avoid conflicts in SPB-Decompiler&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;UPDATE: *Database:* Updated the Database to AIRAC 2410&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;UPDATE: *Database:* Updated the Database for AAU3&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;UPDATE: *Adjust Elevation:* Modified the handling, when no elevation data is available.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;UPDATE: *Maintenance:* Unnecessary code has been removed&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;UPDATE: *Components:* Updated the WebView2 Runtime, OpenDocument components and Xaml-Behaviors components to the most recent version&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;BUGFIX: *LoadLiveries:* Fixed a null-pointer exception on startup, if there are not well designed liveries or aircrafts in the community folder&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;li&gt;BUGFIX: *Marketplace-Data:* Fixed a CTD when editing a heading tag without a heading number in the marketplace description preview window.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
3.5.0.4714&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Bushtrip:* The option to provide a requested (an IFR) flight plan to the air traffic control has been added to the base data.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Waypoints:* Added an option to manually override the altitude of a waypoint to ignore any automatic calculations by BTI or LNM. Useful for altitude restrictions on Navaid waypoints or fictitious restrictions on your trip.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *SimVars:* Added "AMBIENT TEMPERATURE" in SimVarWatcher and A-Vars for PropertyTrigger.&#xD;
FEATURE: *Aircrafts:* Added a cache for the installed aircrafts and liveries.&lt;br&gt; *Behavior Change:* If you install or remove a new aircraft or livery, you need to update the cache manually via Menu &amp;rarr; Tools &amp;rarr; Load Liveries/Aircrafts.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Assistance-Options:* Added the assistance option "ATC Enforce Flightplan".&#xD;
UPDATE: *Translate DeepL-App:* Removal of the note for free DeepL app from the translated string and optimization of the clipboard handling.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Databases:* Updated the databases to City Update 7: European Cities II, Sim Update 15 (30.05.2024), Navdata (AIRAC 2406) + WorldHub (17.06.2024), City Update 8 - LasVegas (20.06.2024), City Update 9 - Northeast USA (02.07.2024), Navdata (AIRAC 2407) + World Hub Updates (11.07.2024), World Update 17 United Kingdom &amp; Ireland (23.07.2024), Navdata (AIRAC 2408) + World Hub Updates (09.08.2024), World Update 18 Germany, Austria, and Switzerland (22.08.2024)&#xD;
UPDATE: *Marketplace:* Added a warning message if there are more than 5 tags defined.&#xD;
UPDATE: *SimConnect:* Updated the MSFS SDK Components and SimConnect binaries to SDK Version 0.24.3.0.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Components:* Updated the Microsoft.Xaml.Behaviors.Wpf, Microsoft.Web.WebView2 and DocumentFormat.OpenXml to the most recent version.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *IngameMarker:* Fixed an issue where the IngameMarker texts were not read correctly from the language table and were fixed to the base language.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *ParkingLot on Waypoints:* An unnecessary warning about a LivingWorld exclusion no longer appears when you add parking lots to a waypoint (HOW????).&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
3.4.1.4648&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Aircraft-List:* The Gotfriends Monster NX has been added to the list of payware aircrafts.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Flightplan:* Fixed issue that prevented adding location information at a stopover airport when landing options were enabled.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
3.4.0.4634 - Ingame POI Reader / Usage-Database&#xD;
FEATURE: *Ingame-POI:* Added the ability to read POIs from MSFS and add-ons. Jump to the POI on the world map and export it for Little Navmap! &#xD;
USER-REQ: *Date/Time:* Set the date/time of a mission to the current date and time when the mission is created.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Aircraft-List:* The Iris PC-21 - PILATUS has been added to the list of payware aircrafts.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Usage-Database:* Added the possibility to remove projects from the usage database.&#xD;
USER-REQ: *Flightplan:* Added the landing option "On ATC Parking Spot" to the flight plan which allows you to define this option individually for each destination airport.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Databases:* Updated the databases for City Update 6 South West Germany&#xD;
UPDATE: *Databases:* Updated the databases to AIRAC 2404 and recent World-Hub changes.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Marketplace-Profiles:* Some minor optimizations when loading marketplace profiles.&#xD;
UPDATE: *License-Key:* Remove blanks from the key before checking it to avoid some user confusion after copying and pasting the key.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Key-Request:* Added a cooldown period between requests to avoid license request spam!&#xD;
BUGFIX: *CTD:* Fixed a crash to desktop on startup if the simulator was not detected correctly.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Airport-Creation:* In the north of France, for some reason, Bing Maps cannot provide elevation data. This prevented the creation of airfields at waypoints.&#xD;
&#xD;
 * 'Usage-Database'* &#xD;
BUGFIX: *Usage-Database:* BTI incorrectly continued to list DME that was previously a VORDME and had been downgraded as a VOR.&lt;br&gt;Please *read the instructions* in USAGEDB-VORDME.txt included in this package to check the DME you are using in your missions.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
</ChangeLog>
  <Downloadlink>https://www.bushtripinjector.de/downloads/</Downloadlink>
  <RequiredDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>14</Minor>
    <Build>5</Build>
    <Revision>2</Revision>
  </RequiredDbVersion>
  <CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>38</Minor>
    <Build>2</Build>
    <Revision>4</Revision>
  </CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
  <CurrentMainDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>38</Minor>
    <Build>2</Build>
    <Revision>4</Revision>
  </CurrentMainDbVersion>
  <CurrentParkingDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>38</Minor>
    <Build>2</Build>
    <Revision>4</Revision>
  </CurrentParkingDbVersion>
  <CurrentNavAidsDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>38</Minor>
    <Build>2</Build>
    <Revision>4</Revision>
  </CurrentNavAidsDbVersion>
</BushTripInjector>