<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BushTripInjector xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" Id="BushTripInjector">
  <MinVersion>
    <Major>0</Major>
    <Minor>10</Minor>
    <Build>3</Build>
    <Revision>1742</Revision>
  </MinVersion>
  <PrevVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>0</Minor>
    <Build>0</Build>
    <Revision>-1</Revision>
  </PrevVersion>
  <CurrentVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>0</Minor>
    <Build>1</Build>
    <Revision>2020</Revision>
  </CurrentVersion>
  <ChangeLog>&lt;meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html;charset=UTF-8'&gt;&#xD;
1.0.1.2020&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: RandomAction, Bugfixes for Discovery&#xD;
FEATURE: *RandomAction:* Added the RandomAction to Events&amp;Triggers Editor for BushTrips and DiscoveryFlights.&lt;br&gt;Use the RandomActions to give the user more variation. Activate sceneries in the vicinity, simulate nature spectacles or simply let animals run in random directions. There are no limits to your creativity.&#xD;
UPDATE: *OpenFileDialog:* Changed the default file filter to all supported file formats.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Discovery:* Handle menu items for DiscoveryFlights. *Please check your current settings after loading DiscoveryFlights.*&#xD;
UPDATE: *MarketPlace:* Added marketplace handling for DiscoveryFlights. &#xD;
UPDATE: *Import XML/SPB:* Added several properties to Import-Parser: DefaultActivated (all triggers), OnScreenTimer (TimerTrigger).&#xD;
UPDATE: *XamlBehaviors:* Updated component to most recent version.&#xD;
UPDATE: *WebView2:* Updated component to most recent version. Several fixes. &#xD;
UPDATE: *ProjectFile:* Save the Weather-file inside of the project-file.&#xD;
UPDATE: *LibraryObject*:  More accurate positioning of objects (6.78cm resolution at equator). (thx goes to Synoxys)&#xD;
UPDATE: *Areas*:  More accurate positioning of areas for Rectangle, Cylinder, Teleport and Landmarks (6.78cm resolution at equator). (thx goes to Synoxys)&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Discovery:* Fixed an issue on generating DicoveryFlights when no translation is present.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Discovery:* Fixed some issues loading the saved vaules in some conditions (Weather, Colors, Menu, Translate...). &#xD;
BUGFIX: *Discovery:* Several small fixes and optimizations for DiscoveryFlight.&#xD;
&#xD;
---&#xD;
1.0.0.1994&#xD;
HIGHLIGHT: DiscoveryFlights&#xD;
Unlocking the DiscoveryFlights for all users. This was made possible by the kind permission and waiver of exclusive rights of a customer on the US West Coast.&lt;br&gt;Create DiscoveryFlights and tell us more about a region. Define landmarks to make users aware of them. Use the Events&amp;Triggers editor to give the user more visual and audible impressions. Choose the music style and volume when approaching a POI. And much more.&#xD;
&#xD;
This Version has many changes in the core functionallity of BushTripInjector because of merging some branches into community version.&lt;br&gt;Despite intensive testing, bugs and problems may occur. If you have an issue, please contact me on &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/fa6mtW2zz4"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;Thank you very much.&#xD;
&#xD;
USER-REQ: Hide the MainWindow while taking images with 3d Image Generator. (Koschi)&#xD;
USER-REQ: Added a checkbox to worldmap sheet to show/hide only selected flightsim.to add-ons. (FronTech)&#xD;
FEATURE: *ProjectFiles:* Save your Mission with all information in a single file (only available for DiscoversFlights yet).&#xD;
FEATURE: *WorldMap:* Added an option to show pins for landmarks on WorldMap. The tooltip of the pin shows you the name of the landmark.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Areas:* Added the AltitudeIsAGL flag to CylinderArea and RectangleArea. Available in Import XML/SPB Module, too.&#xD;
UPDATE: *Waiting Screen:* A waiting screen has been added so as not to inconvenience the users when it takes longer than usual&#xD;
UPDATE: *Typos* As usual, some typos corrected. (Thanks to ProfSC)&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Leg2+:* Fixed an issue when the ProximityTriggers has different Activated/Deactivated Flags.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Leg2+:* Added the Leg2+ workaround for Property-, Airportlanding-, AreaLanding-, Counter- and TimerTrigger, too.&#xD;
BUGFIX: *CruisingAlt:* Fixed an issue with CruisingAlt was not set correctly (BushTrip &amp; Discovery)&#xD;
BUGFIX: *Changelog:* Fixed an issue when viewing the changelog from helpmenu and no parking database is installed.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
</ChangeLog>
  <Downloadlink>https://flightsim.to/file/4131/bushtripinjector</Downloadlink>
  <RequiredDbVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>14</Minor>
    <Build>5</Build>
    <Revision>1</Revision>
  </RequiredDbVersion>
  <CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
    <Major>1</Major>
    <Minor>21</Minor>
    <Build>13</Build>
    <Revision>0</Revision>
  </CurrentMSFSDatabaseVersion>
</BushTripInjector>